A Guide to the Governor Timothy M. Kaine, Policy Office, Records, 2002-2010 (bulk 2006-2009)
Library of Virginia
- II. Regulations, 2003-2010 (accession 44690)., Extent: 14.70 cubic feet (42 boxes). (Box 7-48)
  - EDUCATION, Secretary of
    - Department of Education
      - Regulations for Conducting Division-Level Academic Revies: 8 VAC 20-700, 1627/3889 (Box 16, Folder 2)
      - Regulations Governing the Operation of Proprietary Schools and Issuing of Agent Permits, Repeal Regulation: 8 VAC 20-350, 2213/3872 (Box 16, Folder 3)
      - Amendments to the Regulations Establishing Standards for Accrediting Public Schools in Virginia, 2007 Revisions: 8 VAC 20-131, 2300/4027 (Box 16, Folder 4)
      - Regulations Governing Literacy Loan Applications in Virginia, Revisions to Ensure Alignment with Virginia Code and Appropriate and Necessary Requirements are in Place: 8 VAC 20-100, 2356/4133 (Box 16, Folder 5)
      - Regulations Governing Jointly Owned and Operated Schools and Jointly Operated Programs, Repeal Current Regulation and Promulgate New Regulations: 8 VAC 20-281, 2358/4135 (Box 16, Folder 6)
      - Regulations Governing Textbooks, Free or Rental Systems State Aid, Repeal: 8 VAC 20-190, 2407/4194 (Box 16, Folder 7)
      - Licensure Regulations for School Personnel, Repeal Text: 8 VAC 20-22, 1844/4128 (Box 16, Folder 8)
      - Regulations Governing the Review and Approval of Education Programs in Virginia, Promulgate New Regulations to Align with State and Federal Laws and Regulations: 8 VAC 20-542, 1891/4129 (Box 16, Folder 9)
      - Revision of Information Requirements for Secondary School Transcripts and Profile Data Sheets: 8 VAC 20-160, 1885/4093 (Box 16, Folder 10)
      - Regulations Governing Local School Boards and School Divisions, Repeal Outdated Regulations and Consolidate Applicable Sections into New Regulations: 8 VAC 20-720, 2390/4172 (Box 16, Folder 11)
      - Pupil Transportation including Minimum Standards for School Buses in Virginia: 8 VAC 20-70, 2509/4377 (Box 16, Folder 12)
      - Regulations Governing Special Education Programs for Children with Disabilities in Virginia, Revisions to Comply with the "Individuals with Disabilities Education Improvement Act of 2004" and its Federal Implementation Regulations: 8 VAC 20-80, 2221/4353 (Box 16, Folder 13)
      - Regulations Governing Student Insurance Program, Repeal: 8 VAC 20-500, 2408/4195 (Box 16, Folder 14)
      - Regulations Governing Educational Services for Gifted Students, Revision of Regulations School Divisions Must Meet in their Gifted Education Programs, K-12: 8 VAC 20-40, 1933/4193 (Box 16, Folder 15)
      - Regulations Governing the Determination of Critical Teacher Shortage Areas for Awarding the Virginia Teaching Scholarship Loan Program: 8 VAC 20-650, 2545/4433 (Box 16, Folder 16)
      - Governing Jointly Owned and Operated Schools and Jointly Operated Programs: 8 VAC 20-281, 2358/4419 (Box 16, Folder 17)
      - Regulations Governing Local School Boards and School Divisions, Incorporate Textbook Provisions into Consolidated Regulations: 8 VAC 20-720, 2668/4646 (Box 16, Folder 18)
      - Regulations Governing Local School Boards and School Divisions, Promulgate Regulation, Consolidate other Select Regulations Related to Local School Boards: 8 VAC 20-720, 2658/4633 (Box 16, Folder 19)
      - State Board of Education Regulations Establishing Standards for Accrediting Public Schools in Virginia: 8 VAC 20-131, 2300/4541 (Box 16, Folder 20)
      - Regulations Governing the Operation of Private Day Schools for Students with Disabilities and Educational Programs Offered in Group Homes and Residential Facilities in the Commonwealth, Promulgate Regulations for Licensure of Education Programs: 8 VAC 20-671, 2727/4715 (Box 17, Folder 1)
      - State Board of Elections, Regulations Governing Public Participation, Fast Track, Promulgate Regulations Governing Public Participation: 8 VAC 20-11, 2797/4801 (Box 17, Folder 2)
      - Regulations Governing Local School Boards and School Divisions, Incorporate Provisions on Fees and Charges as New Section of 8 VAC 20-720: 8 VAC 20-720, 2719/4704 (Box 17, Folder 3)
      - Regulations Governing Special Education Programs for Children with Disabilities in Virginia, Revisions to Comply with the "Individuals with Disabilities Education Improvement Act of 2004" and its Federal Implementation Regulations: 8 VAC 20-80, 2221/4828 (Box 17, Folder 4)
      - Regulations Governing the Determination of Critical Teacher Shortage Areas for Awarding the Virginia Teaching Scholarship Loan Program, Fast Track: Chapter 650, Section 30, Align Criteria with Code, Career Technical Education: 8 VAC 20-650, 2894/4913 (Box 17, Folder 5)
      - Regulations Governing Reduction of State Aid when Length of School Terms Below 180 Teaching Days or 990 Teach Hours, Chapter 520, Annual Compliance Report Timeline, Minor Revision to Regulation: 8 VAC 20-521, 2828/4827 (Box 17, Folder 6)
      - Regulations Establishing Standards for Accrediting Public Schools in Virginia, 2007-2008 Revisions: 8 VAC 20-131, 2300/4543 (Box 17, Folder 7)
      - Regulations Governing Pupil Transportation Including Minimum Standards for School Buses in Virginia, Amend Chapter 70, Pupil Transportation Regulations, Update the Regulations Based on New Technology and Other Changes in Pupil Transportation in Virginia: 8 VAC 20-70, 2509/4920 (Box 17, Folder 8)
      - Regulations Governing Jointly Owned and Operated Schools and Jointly Operated Programs, Repeal Current Regulation (8 VAC 280) and Promulgate New Regulations (8 VAC 20-281): 8 VAC 20-281, 2358/5135 (Box 17, Folder 9)
      - Regulations Governing Local School Boards and School Divisions, Promulgate Regulation, Consolidate Other Select Regulations Related to Local School Boards: 8 VAC 20-720, 2658/5134 (Box 17, Folder 10)
      - Regulations Governing Unexcused Absences and Truancy, Promulgate Regulation to Govern the Collection and Reporting of Truancy-Related Data: 8 VAC 20-730, 3148/5305 (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - Library of Virginia
      - Regulations Governing the Destruction of Public Records Containing Social Security Numbers: 17 VAC 15-120, 1660/4079 (Box 17, Folder 12)
      - Regulations Governing the Destruction of Public Records Containing Social Security Numbers: 17 VAC 15-120, 1660/4691 (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - State Council of Higher Education for Virginia
      - Certification of Certain Institutions to Confer Degrees, Diplomas and Certificates: 8 VAC 40-31, 1621/3483 (Box 17, Folder 14)
      - Certification of Certain Institutions to Confer Degrees, Diplomas and Certificates - Repeal Chapter 30: 8 VAC 40-31, 1621/3679 (Box 17, Folder 15)
      - Certification of Certain Institutions to Confer Degrees, Diplomas and Certificates: 8 VAC 40-31, 3048/5150 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - FINANCE, Secretary of
    - Department of Taxation
      - Virginia Slaughter Hog and Feeder Pig Excise Tax, Repeal of Regulations that are Made Obsolete by Statutory Changes: 23 VAC 10-70, 2053/3675 (Box 18, Folder 1)
      - Virginia Soft Drink Excise Tax Regulations, Repeal of Selected Soft Drink Tax Regulations that Provide No Additional Guidance to Clear and Ambiguous Statutes: 23 VAC 10-390, 2084/3710 (Box 18, Folder 2)
      - Watercraft Sales and Use Tax, Repeal of One Watercraft Sales and Use Tax Regulation that is Obsolete Due to a Statutory Change: 23 VAC 10-230, 2099/3726 (Box 18, Folder 3)
      - Income Tax Withholding, Repeal of Selected Income Tax Withholding Regulations that Provide No Additional Guidance to Clear and Ambiguous Statutes: 23 VAC 10-140, 2088/3714 (Box 18, Folder 4)
      - Repeal of Selected Declaration of Estimated Income Tax by Individuals Tax Regulations that Provide No Additional Guidance to Clear and Unambiguous Statutes: 23 VAC 10-112, 2114/3744 (Box 18, Folder 5)
      - Repeal of Tax on Wills and Administration Regulation Section that Provide No Additional Guidance to Clear and Unambiguous Statutes: 23 VAC 10-310, 2092/3718 (Box 18, Folder 6)
      - Repeal of Cigarette Tax Regulations that are Obsolete Due to Statutory Changes: 23 VAC 10-370, 2090/3716 (Box 18, Folder 7)
      - Repeal of Four Soybean Excise Tax Regulations that Provide No Additional Guidance to Clear and Unambiguous Statutes: 23 VAC 10-75, 2097/3724 (Box 18, Folder 8)
      - Repeal of Selected Litter Tax Regulations that Provide No Additional Guidance to Clear and Unambiguous Statutes: 23 VAC 10-360, 2111/3741 (Box 18, Folder 9)
      - Repeal of Forest Product Tax Regulations that are Obsolete Due to Statutory Changes: 23 VAC 10-350, 2104/3733 (Box 18, Folder 10)
      - Repeal of Two Aircraft Sales and Use Tax Regulations that Provide No Additional Guidance to Clear and Unambiguous Statutes: 23 VAC 10-220, 2100/3728 (Box 18, Folder 11)
      - Repeal of Selected Fiduciary Income Tax Regulations that Provide No Additional Guidance to Clear and Ambiguous Statutes: 23 VAC 10-115, 2112/3742 (Box 18, Folder 12)
      - Retail Sales and Use Tax, Action to Amend "Churches" Regulation: 23 VAC 10-210, 2193/3849 (Box 18, Folder 13)
      - Retail Sales and Use Tax, Action to Amend Medicines, Drugs: 23 VAC 10-210, 2197/3854 (Box 18, Folder 14)
      - Numerous Regulations that Seek to Repeal Sections of the Tax Codes that are No Longer Valid: 3769, 3765, 3732, 3708, 3729, 3713, 3720, 3743, 3711, 3725, 3715, 3717, 3734, 3757, 3723, 3721, 3719, 3709, 3766, 3751 and 3707 (Box 18, Folder 15)
      - Retail Sales and Use Tax, Action to Amend "Hospitals and Nursing Homes" Regulation: 23 VAC 10-210, 2194/3850 (Box 18, Folder 16)
      - Retail Sales and Use Tax, Contractor Respecting Real Estate: 23 VAC 10-210, 2196/3852 (Box 18, Folder 17)
      - Retail Sales and Use Tax, Action to Amend "Advertising Definitions" Regulation: 23 VAC 10-210, 2198/3855 (Box 18, Folder 18)
      - Retail Sales and Use Tax, Action to Amend "Newspaper and Other Media Advertising" Regulation: 23 VAC 10-210, 220/3857 (Box 18, Folder 19)
      - Retail Sales and Use Tax, Action to Amend "In-house Advertising" Regulation: 23 VAC 10-210, 2201/3858 (Box 18, Folder 20)
      - Retail Sales and Use Tax, Action to Amend "Advertising Businesses" Regulation: 23 VAC 10-220, 2199/3856 (Box 18, Folder 21)
      - Retail Sales and Use Tax, Motor Vehicle Refinishers, Painters and Car Washers: 23 VAC 10-210, 2240/3929 (Box 18, Folder 22)
      - Retail Sales and Use Tax, Pollution Control Equipment and Facilities: 23 VAC 10-210, 2241/3930 (Box 18, Folder 23)
      - Retail Sales and Use Tax, Fabrications: 23 VAC 10-210, 2243/3932 (Box 18, Folder 24)
      - Retail Sales and Use Tax, Penalties and Interest, Audits: 23 VAC 10-210, 2242/3931 (Box 18, Folder 25)
      - Retail Sales and Use Tax, Maintenance Contracts and Warranty Plans: 23 VAC 10-210, 2238/3927 (Box 18, Folder 26)
      - Retail Sales and Use Tax, Manufacturing and Processing: 23 VAC 10-210, 2239/3928 (Box 18, Folder 27)
      - Retail Sales and Use Tax, Gifts Purchased in Virginia: 23 VAC 10-210, 2195/3851 (Box 18, Folder 28)
      - Retail Sales and Use Tax, Leases and Rentals: 23 VAC 10-210, 2237/3926 (Box 18, Folder 29)
      - Retail Sales and Use Tax, Hotels, Motels, Tourist Camps, etc.: 23 VAC 10-210, 2236/3925 (Box 18, Folder 30)
      - Retail Sales and Use Tax, Action to Amend Occasional Sales Regulations: 23 VAC 10-210, 2235/3922 (Box 18, Folder 31)
      - Amendment of the Retail Sales and Use Tax Government Contractors Regulation to Conform to Item 268 of the 2006 Budget Bill: 23 VAC 10-210, 2411/4202 (Box 18, Folder 32)
      - Repeal of Twenty-Seven Motor Vehicle Fuel Sales Tax Regulations that Provide No Additional Guidance to Clear and Unambiguous Statutes: 23 VAC 10-240 (Box 18, Folder 33)
      - Amendment of the Corporate Income Tax Regulation to Add a Section Regarding Intangible Expenses Paid to Related Entities: 23 VAC 10-120, 2327/4070 (Box 18, Folder 34)
      - Public Participation Guidelines, Reflect Changes in Administrative Process Act: 23 VAC 10-10, 2449/4275 (Box 18, Folder 35)
      - Retail Sales and Use Tax, Amendment to Reflect Legislative Changes Concerning the Printing Industry: 23 VAC 10-210, 2455/4285 (Box 18, Folder 36)
      - Retail Sales and Use Tax, Amendment of the Florist and Nurseryman Regulation Section to Provide Clarification and to Reflect Changes in Policy: 23 VAC 10-210-610, 2463/4295 (Box 18, Folder 37)
      - Retail Sales and Use Tax, New Regulation to Govern Application of the Exemption Provided for Audiovisual Production: 23 VAC 10-210, 2454/4282 (Box 18, Folder 38)
      - Promulgation of Business, Professional and Occupational License (BPOL) Tax Regulations from the 2000 BPOL Guidelines: 23 VAC 10-500, 2461/4291 (Box 18, Folder 39)
      - Amendment of the Retail Sales and Use Tax Government Contractors Regulation Section to Conform to Item 268 of the 2006 Budget Bill: 23 VAC 10-210, 2411/4587 (Box 19, Folder 1)
      - Amendment of the Watercraft Sales and Use Tax Regulations and the Retail Sales and Use Tax Regulation: 23 VAC 10-230, 2721/4708 (Box 19, Folder 2)
      - General Provisions Applicable to All Taxes Administered by the Department of Taxation, Promulgation of an Administrative Appeals Regulation Section 23 VAC 10-20-165 and Amendment of Existing Regulation Sections to be Consistent with the New Section: 23 VAC 10-20, 2537/4418 (Box 19, Folder 3)
      - Public Participation Guidelines, Model Public Participation Guidelines: 23 VAC 10-11, 2724/4716 (Box 19, Folder 4)
      - Retail Sales and Use Tax, Maintenance Contracts and Warranty Plans: 23 VAC 10-210, 2238/4550 (Box 19, Folder 5)
      - Virginia Slaughter Hog and Feeder Pig Excise Tax Regulations: 23 VAC 10-70, 2053/4296 (Box 19, Folder 6)
      - Retail Sales and Use Tax, Penalties and Interest, Audits: 23 VAC 10-210, 2242/4721 (Box 19, Folder 7)
      - Retail Sales and Use Tax, Action to Amend "Churches" Regulation: 23 VAC 10-210, 2193/5017 (Box 19, Folder 8)
      - Retail Sales and Use Tax, Motor Vehicle Refinishers, Painters and Car Washers: 23 VAC 10-210, 2240/4804 (Box 19, Folder 9)
      - Retail Sales and Use Tax, Penalties and Interest, Audits: 23 VAC 10-210, 2242/5158 (Box 19, Folder 10)
      - Retail Sales and Use Tax, Maintenance Contracts and Warranty Plans: 23 VAC 10-210, 2238/5159 (Box 19, Folder 11)
      - Retail Sales and Use Tax, Motor Vehicle Refinishers, Painters and Car Washers: 23 VAC 10-210, 2240/5339 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - HEALTH AND HUMAN RESOURCES, Secretary of
    - Department for the Aging
      - The Virginia Public Guardian and Conservator Program: 22 VAC 5-30, 1805/3256 (Box 19, Folder 13)
      - The Virginia Public Guardian and Conservator Program, New Regulation: 22 VAC 5-30, 1805/4413 (Box 19, Folder 14)
      - The Virginia Guardian and Conservator Program, New Regulation: 22 VAC 5-30, 1805/4084 (Box 19, Folder 14a)
    - Department for the Blind and Vision Impaired
      - Regulations Governing Provisions of Services in Vocational Rehabilitation, Repeal Existing Regulation and Promulgate New Regulations: 22 VAC 45-51, 2588/4506 (Box 19, Folder 15)
    - Department of Health
      - Biosolids Use, Certification of Land Appliers: 12 VAC 5-585, 1592/2874 (Box 19, Folder 16)
      - Disease Reporting and Control: 12 VAC 5-90, 1595/2884 (Box 19, Folder 17)
      - Biosolids Use, Enforcement and Site Management: 12 VAC 5-585, 1684/3069 (Box 19, Folder 18)
      - Disease Reporting and Control, Quarantine and Isolation: 12 VAC 5-90, 1626/3089 (Box 19, Folder 19)
      - Expansion of Virginia Newborn Screening Services: 12 VAC 5-71, 1842/3331 (Box 19, Folder 20)
      - Disease Reporting and Control: 12 VAC 5-90, 1616/3589 (Box 19, Folder 21)
      - Bedding and Upholstered Furniture Inspection Program: 12 VAC 5-125, 1419/3318 (Box 19, Folder 22)
      - Onsite Sewage Regulation: 12 VAC 5-611, 1955/3508 (Box 19, Folder 23)
      - Virginia Medical Services Regulations, Adoption of Regulations Addressing the Designation of Regional Emergency Medical Services Council Designation and the Rescue Squad Assistance Fund: 12 VAC 5-31, 1169/3614 (Box 19, Folder 24)
      - Biosolids Use, Certification of Land Appliers: 12 VAC 5-585, 1592/3434 (Box 19, Folder 25)
      - Board of Health Regulations, Amendment in Accordance with a Recent Court Case: 12 VAC 5-550, 2192/3248 (Box 19, Folder 26)
      - Expansion of Newborn Screening Services: 12 VAC 5-71, 1842/3648 (Box 19, Folder 27)
      - Repeal Existing Regulations and Adopt New Regulations Containing Up-To-Date Radiological Health Standards: 12 VAC 5-480, 895/3643 (Box 20, Folder 1)
      - Regulations Governing Provisions of Services in Vocational Rehabilitation: 22 VAC 45-51, 1923/3647 (Box 20, Folder 2)
      - Biosolids Use Regulations, 2006 Fee Amendment: 12 VAC 5-585, 2705/3697 (Box 20, Folder 3)
      - Waterworks Regulations, Emergency Management Plan for Community Waterworks: 12 VAC 5-590, 1640/3666 (Box 20, Folder 4)
      - State Plan for the Provision of Children's Specialty Services (REPEAL): 12 VAC 5-190, 1590/3510 (Box 20, Folder 5)
      - Proposed Repeal of VAC Codified Plan Followed by Implementation of a Guidance Document: 12 VAC 5-60, 1311/3558 (Box 20, Folder 6)
      - Biosolids Use, Enforcement and Site Management: 12 VAC 5-585, 1684/3453 (Box 20, Folder 7)
      - Amendment of Fee Schedule: 12 VAC 5-490, 2191/3847 (Box 20, Folder 8)
      - Regulations for Disease Reporting and Control, Regulations for Reporting Healthcare Associated Infections: 12 VAC 5-90, 2212/3871 (Box 20, Folder 9)
      - Regulations Governing Virginia Newborn Screening Services/Expansion of Newborn Screening Services: 12 VAC 5-71, 1842/3923 (Box 20, Folder 10)
      - Regulations for Disease Reporting and Control: 12 VAC 5-90, 2212/4032 (Box 20, Folder 11)
      - State Plan for the Children with Special Health Care Needs Program: 12 VAC 5-191, 1590/4138 (Box 20, Folder 12)
      - Regulations for Bedding and Upholstered Furniture Inspection Program, New Regulation: 12 VAC 5-125, 1419/4041 (Box 20, Folder 13)
      - Biosolids Use, Certification of Land Appliers: 12 VAC 5-585, 1592/4132 (Box 20, Folder 14)
      - Regulations Governing the Virginia Physician Loan Repayment Program, Adoption of Regulations to Administer a Loan Repayment Program: 12 VAC 5-508, 716/4008 (Box 20, Folder 15)
      - Virginia Emergency Medical Services Regulations, Adoption of Regulations Addressing the Designation of Regional Emergency Medical Services (EMS) Council Designation and the Rescue Squad Assistance Fund (RSAF): 12 VAC 5-31, 1169/4269 (Box 20, Folder 16)
      - Biosolids Use Regulations, Enforcement and Site Management: 12 VAC 5-585, 1684/4163 (Box 20, Folder 17)
      - Regulations Governing Durable Do Not Resuscitate Orders, Improve Processes and Ensure Consistent Care Throughout the Healthcare Continuum: 12 VAC 5-66, 2520/4392 (Box 20, Folder 18)
      - Regulations for the Licensure of Hospices, Hospice Program Changes: 12 VAC 5-391, 2462/4293 (Box 20, Folder 19)
      - Virginia Emergency Medical Services Regulations, Include New Regulations as a Result of Legislative Changes and Changes in Practice of EMS: 12 VAC 5-31, 2446/4270 (Box 20, Folder 20)
      - State Medical Facilities Plan: 12 VAC 5-230, 240-360, 1190/4004 (Box 20, Folder 21)
      - Emergency Regulation to Require the Reporting of Certain Methicillin-Resistant Staphylococcus aureus (MRSA) Infections: 12 VAC 5-90, 2511/4379 (Box 20, Folder 22)
      - Disease Reporting and Control, Reporting Healthcare-Associated Infections: 12 VAC 5-90, 2212/4382 (Box 20, Folder 23)
      - Regulations for the Immunization of School Children: 12 VAC 5-110, 2593/4516 (Box 20, Folder 24)
      - Regulations Governing the State Dental Scholarship Program, Amend Regulation Following Periodic Review: 12 VAC 5-520, 2624/4570 (Box 20, Folder 25)
      - Regulations Implementing the Virginia Organ and Tissue Donor Registry, Amendment for Clarity, Efficiency and Effectiveness: 12 VAC 5-475, 2631/4583 (Box 20, Folder 26)
      - Virginia Hearing Impairment Identification and Monitoring System, Amend the Regulations as a Result of Periodic Review: 12 VAC 5-80, 2634/4586 (Box 20, Folder 27)
      - Regulations for Inpatient Hospital Licensure, Repeal of Sections in 12 VAC 5-410 with Promulgation of a New Regulation: 12 VAC 5-411, 2622/4567 (Box 20, Folder 28)
      - State Board of Health Virginia Radiation Protection Regulations, Amendment of Fee Schedule: 12 VAC 5-490, 2191/4281 (Box 21, Folder 1)
      - Regulations for Disease Reporting and Control, Requiring MRSA Reporting: 12 VAC 5-90, 2511/4500 (Box 21, Folder 2)
      - Virginia Radiation Protection Regulations Fee Schedule for X-ray Fees: 12 VAC 5-490, 2453/4515 (Box 21, Folder 3)
      - Regulations for the Licensure of Hospices, Hospice Program Changes: 12 VAC 5-391, 2462/4468 (Box 21, Folder 4)
      - Waterworks Regulations, Chronically Noncompliant Waterworks: 12 VAC 5-590, 2743/4733 (Box 21, Folder 5)
      - Onsite Sewage Regulations, Adopt New Performance-Based Regulations Pertaining to Locating, Designing, Constructing and Operating Onsite Sewage Systems: 12 VAC 5-611, 2609/4538 (Box 21, Folder 6)
      - Regulations for Testing Children for Elevated Blood-Lead Levels, Amend Lead-Testing Regulations to Reflect New Statutory Requirements: 12 VAC 5-120, 2428/4624 (Box 21, Folder 7)
      - State Medical Facilities Plan, Comprehensive SMFP Revision: 12 VAC 5-230, 1190/4707 (Box 21, Folder 8)
      - Regulations for Disease Reporting and Control, 2008 Update: 12 VAC 5-90, 2775/4768 (Box 21, Folder 9)
      - Advance Health Care Directive Registry: 12 VAC 5-67, 2748/4738 (Box 21, Folder 10)
      - Regulations for Disease Reporting and Control, Regulations Requiring MRSA Reporting: 12 VAC 5-90, 2511/4857 (Box 21, Folder 11)
      - Virginia Radiation Protection Regulations, Fee Schedule, Amendment of Fee Schedule: 12 VAC 5-490, 2191/4855 (Box 21, Folder 12)
      - Board of Health Regulations Governing Vital Records, Amendment in Accordance with a Recent Court Case: 12 VAC 5-550, 2192/4617 (Box 21, Folder 13)
      - Regulations for the Immunization of School Children, Update of the Regulations: 12 VAC 5-110, 2593/4858 (Box 21, Folder 14)
      - Establishment of the Virginia Immunization Information System: 12 VAC 5-115, 3071/5183 (Box 21, Folder 15)
      - Regulations for the Onsite Sewage Indemnification Fund, Implement Section 32.1-164.1:01 of the Code of Virginia: 12 VAC 5-612, 2608/4854 (Box 21, Folder 16)
      - New Regulations Establishing a Uniform Schedule of Civil Penalties for Violations of Onsite Sewage and Alternative Discharging Sewage Treatment System Regulations: 12 VAC 5-650, 2610/4859 (Box 21, Folder 17)
      - Virginia Radiation Protection Regulations, Fingerprinting Update with Contact Information: 12 VAC 5-481, 2984/5046 (Box 21, Folder 18)
      - Regulations for Disease Reporting and Control, Expanded Requirements for Reporting Healthcare-Associated Infections: 12 VAC 5-90, 3122/5258 (Box 21, Folder 19)
      - Regulations Governing Durable Do Not Resuscitate Orders, Amend to Improve Processes and Ensure Consistent Care throughout the Healthcare Continuum: 12 VAC 5-66, 2520/5048 (Box 21, Folder 20)
      - Regulations for Testing Children for Elevated Blood-Lead Levels, Amend Lead-Testing Regulations to Reflect New Statutory Requirements: 12 VAC 5-120, 2428/5196 (Box 21, Folder 21)
      - Regulations for Disease Reporting and Control, 2008 Update: 12 VAC 5-90, 2775/5049 (Box 21, Folder 22)
      - Advance Health Care Directive Registry, Implement a Secure Online Registry for Citizens to Submit Advance Health Care Directive: 12 VAC 5-67, 2748/4738 (Box 21, Folder 23)